CHRISTIAN DELOS REYES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

☑ Christian.dreyes@gmail.com 📞 6474502159 👂 Toronto, Canada in christianDReyes 🖸 itiand

SUMMARY

Web developer with deep interest in the intersection of technology, design, and human interaction. Highly curious and continually tinkering with interactive and visual elements of the web. I enjoy creating engaging web experiences with a keen eye for aesthetics and detail.

SKILLS

Languages: SASS, Javascript, Ruby, CSS, HTML

Frameworks and Libraries: Node, React, jQuery, EJS, SASS, Ruby on Rails, Express, Bootsrap, Tailwind, ThreeJs

Databases and Systems: PostreSQL, Git/Github, MySQL

Testing: Cypress, Jest, Mocha/Chai

EMPLOYMENT

Fantastic Furniture, Customer Care and Fulfillment Coordinator, Sydney, Australia

Apr. 2021 - June 2022

- Acted as the primary liaison for all nationwide retail, supplier, logistic, and corporate operations, managing daily correspondence with stakeholders and customers.
- Managed a portfolio of customer and stakeholder claims, mainly purchase warranties and logistical discrepancies, by liaising with various departments such as Customer Care, Logistics, Retail, and Warehouse teams.
- Handled online order fulfillments, coordinated with third-party suppliers regarding products and scheduled deliveries.
- Managed multiple concurrent chat inquiries, providing product details, coordinating deliveries, and evaluating warranty claims.

Jujube Australia, Field Coordinator, Mildura, Australia

Feb. 2020 - June 2020

- Oversaw a team of 15-25 jujube pickers, facilitating efficient operations and ensuring seamless flow between harvesting and packing stages.
- In charge of daily equipment preparations and task delegation on the farm, ensuring accurate allocation of resources and capturing details of jujube harvests, including yields and completed rows.
- Carried out record keeping taks and prepared daily summaries, highlighting inventory status and overview of the day's operations and yields.

State Street, Pricing Analyst, Toronto, Ontario

Oct. 2017 - Oct. 2018

- Conducted daily valuation of thousands of securities using real-time market data, ensuring precise price determination and resolving discrepancies and any deviations from set tolerance levels.
- Analyzed and priced a high volume of securities, monitoring market trends and corporate actions/events, and leveraging financial instruments such as Bloomberg, Reuters, and Excel.
- Prepared and delivered daily pricing reports to stakeholders within tight deadlines, while also ensuring timely receipt of all pricing feeds and backup sources, promptly rectifying any pricing deviations.

PROJECTS

Photolabs July 2023

A desktop application designed with React, which functions as an interactive stock photo gallery. The application enhances user experience by offering features like photo 'liking', topic-based filtering, and recommendations for similar images.

Foldr July 2023

A platform that facilitates the sharing and curating of coding resources. The application offers features to browse other users' resources, save desired ones to a personal collection, and provide comments, enabling a community-driven learning experience.

Tweeter June 2023

A single-page, Twitter-like application. Leveraged AJAX, jQuery, HTML5, and CSS3 to create a seamless front-end experience, providing a simplified, user-friendly platform for microblogging.

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs
Diploma: Fullstack Web Developmment

May 2023 - Aug. 2020

Toronto Metropolitan UniversityBachelor of Arts: International Economics and Finance

Sept. 2013 - Apr. 2017

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES

Illustration | Hiking/Backpacking | Film Photography | Basketball